

Curriculum Vitae of: Kathy M. Denson, CPA, CFF, CFE

July, 2014

GENERAL BACKGROUND

The majority of Ms. Denson's career has been devoted to investigative auditing and the measurement of damages. In addition to investigative auditing, Ms. Denson performed financial statement audits for three years. Ms. Denson is responsible for the evaluation of a variety of damages. She has extensive experience in the review of insurance claims for economic and physical damages in a variety of businesses and industries. Ms. Denson has also provided litigation support services, including expert witness testimony, pertaining to a variety of businesses and industries.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts — 1983 NORTHEASTERN ILLINOIS UNIVERSITY, Chicago, Illinois

PROFESSIONAL STATUS

Shareholder, Insight Forensic Accountants, S.C.
Certified Public Accountant since 1986
Certified Fraud Examiner since 1993
Certified in Financial Forensics since 2008
Member, Colorado Society of Certified Public Accountants
Member, American Institute of Certified Public Accountants
Member, Colorado Chapter of Certified Fraud Examiners

Member, Association of Certified Fraud Examiners

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Insight Forensic Accountants, S.C. — 1996 to Present Cordes & Company — 1992 to 1996
Van Schooneveld & Company, Inc. — 1989 to 1992
Campos & Stratis, S.C. — 1985 to 1988

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Agricultural Damages
- · Breach of Fiduciary Duty
- · Business Interruption
- · Business Valuation
- · Construction Bond Claims
- · Economic Loss Analysis
- Environmental Issues
- Employee Dishonesty / Fidelity Bond
- Extra Expense
- · Financial Condition / Motive
- Fraud
- Intellectual Property
- Inventory and Other Contents Loss
- Jeweler & Furrier Block
- · Liability Matters
- Loss of Profits
- · Personal Injury
- Subrogation
- Surety Bond
- Theft
- · Wrongful Dismissal

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

- Agriculture
- Airlines
- Banking
- Chemical Processing
- Churches / Religious Institutions
- Construction
- Dentistry
- Distribution
- Egg / Food Production
- Electronics
- Entertainment
- Hardware / Software
- Hospitals / Health Maintenance
- Hospitality
- Manufacturing
- Meat Processing
- Medical Device Production
- Mercantile / Retail Sales
- Not for Profit
- Oil Refineries
- Paper, Plastics and Printing
- Pharmaceutical
- Professional Service Firms
- Property Management
- Real Estate Development
- Restaurants
- Schools
- Service
- Steel / Heavy Manufacturing
- · Textiles / Apparel
- Transportation
- Utilities
- Wholesale